Today we're going to have some fun talking about some antique-like, types of things, collectibles mostly that, that you can still buy that are sleepers, that are imports.
These imports are going to be really exciting but before I talk about those, let me talk about me, for a minute.
Let?s make it about me.
Like I said, my name is Jan and I have an antique store in Pomona, it's called Antique Avenue.
I used to be a College Administrator but I hated it, boring, so I decided to become an antique appraiser, which is a heck of a lot more fun and it's more relevant, if you ask me.
So I decided to be an antique appraiser and I opened my shop, in Pomona and so you can come anytime.
Bring your trash or treasure and we'll take a look at it for you.
So, that's my expertise, trash and treasure, very exciting.
So today, like I said, we're going to be talking about imports and we're going to focus on Japan.
Japan has different date lines and we're going to start covering those.
What you should look for, and how to identify, the Japan date lines, in terms of the names on the bottom of the cups and how they're made.
So, Japan, occupied Japan, which one is it?
Should I buy it?
Maybe not but we'll find out today on our segment about imports.